freead1.net 2018-03-29

# Privacy Policy

### \- Liability for content

Freead1.net can not guarantee the accuracy, integrity and actuality of the content. In cases of declaration of violation of rights, Freead1.net will delete the concerned content at the soonest possible time.

### \- Google Privacy Policy

The Google Privacy Policy describes how Google and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use Google services, including information provided when you use [FreeAd1.net](http://freead1.net/ "FreeAd1.net - Free Classified Ads"). 

* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.

* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)

* The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

### \- Collection and processing of personal data

Ads on [FreeAd1.net](http://freead1.net/ "FreeAd1.net - Free Classified Ads") are made available to the public. We collect and store the following personal information:

Email address, Computer sign-in data, statistics on page views, other information including your IP address and standard web log information.

We point out that data transmission over the Internet (eg communication via e-mail) can lead to security issues. A complete protection of data against access of third parties is not possible.

### \- Transfer of personal data

Transfer or provision of personal data to a third party occurs only if [FreeAd1.net](http://freead1.net/ "FreeAd1.net - Free Classified Ads") is lawfully obligated to provide information to authorities in relation to an ad that a user has posted, or if the user has given prior consent to the release of personal data. Otherwise, personal data will not be released, shared or sold to third parties for marketing or advertising purposes without prior permission from the user.

### \- Cookies

Freead1.net uses "cookies" in connection with the web browser for optimum usage of the site. A "cookie“ is a small piece of data coming from our web server that is stored in the user's hard drive or other storage device. The user may choose to disable or adjust enabled cookies accordingly by configuring their web browser. Disabling or deleting cookies may result in the unavailability of some functions of the website.

### \- Use of Facebook Social Plugins

Our website uses plugins provided by the social network Facebook.com. The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo or the Like button. For a full list of Facebook plugins please see: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>.

When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of our website with your IP address. If you click the FB "Like" button while you are logged in on Facebook, the content of our page can be linked on your Facebook profile. Therefore if you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. For more information, please visit Facebook's privacy policy: [http://facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php "Facebook's privacy policy").

If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your Facebook member data, please log off Facebook before entering our website.

### \- Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help analyze the usage of the site.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

### \- Right of withdrawal and information

Personal information provided to Freead1.net may be requested for deletion at any time provided that the information is not needed for a running transaction or is not lawfully required for safekeeping. If you have given the permission for the transmission of personal information to a third party, you may at any time cancel or withdraw this permission. Information regarding all personal information saved on Freead1.net can be provided on request and free of cost. You have the possibility of requesting eventual corrections to erroneous and non-current data at any point.

### \- Responsible authority

Questions regarding data privacy and protection should be addressed to contact form.

Copyright © 2009 - 2018 Freead1.net. All rights reserved.
